[
  {
    "front": "academic",
    "back": "a. 学术的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˌækəˈdɛmɪk/"
  },
  {
    "front": "achieve",
    "back": "vt. 实现，达到",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈtʃiːv/"
  },
  {
    "front": "acquire",
    "back": "vt. 获得，取得",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈkwaɪə/"
  },
  {
    "front": "adapt",
    "back": "vt. 使适应",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈdæpt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "adequate",
    "back": "a. 足够的",
    "note": "IELTS"
  },
  {
    "front": "adjust",
    "back": "vt. 调整，调节",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈdʒʌst/"
  },
  {
    "front": "administration",
    "back": "n. 管理，行政",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ədˌmɪnəˈstɹeɪʃən/"
  },
  {
    "front": "adult",
    "back": "n. 成年人",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈdʌlt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "affect",
    "back": "vt. 影响",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈfɛkt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "alter",
    "back": "vt. 改变",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈɑl.tɚ/"
  },
  {
    "front": "alternative",
    "back": "n. 供替代的选择",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ɒl.ˈtɜː(ɹ).nə.tɪv/"
  },
  {
    "front": "analysis",
    "back": "n. 分析",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈnælɪsɪs/"
  },
  {
    "front": "annual",
    "back": "a. 每年的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈæn.ju.əl/"
  },
  {
    "front": "anticipate",
    "back": "vt. 预期",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ænˈtɪs.ɪ.peɪt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "apparent",
    "back": "a. 明显的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈpæ.ɹənt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "approach",
    "back": "n. 方法，途径",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈpɹəʊt͡ʃ/"
  },
  {
    "front": "appropriate",
    "back": "a. 适当的",
    "note": "IELTS"
  },
  {
    "front": "aspect",
    "back": "n. 方面",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈæspɛkt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "assess",
    "back": "vt. 评估",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈsɛs/"
  },
  {
    "front": "assist",
    "back": "vt. 协助",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈsɪst/"
  },
  {
    "front": "assume",
    "back": "vt. 假设",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈsuːm/"
  },
  {
    "front": "attitude",
    "back": "n. 态度",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈætɪˌtjuːd/"
  },
  {
    "front": "attribute",
    "back": "vt. 归因于",
    "note": "IELTS"
  },
  {
    "front": "authority",
    "back": "n. 权威",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ɔːˈθɒɹəti/"
  },
  {
    "front": "available",
    "back": "a. 可利用的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈveɪləb(ə)l/"
  },
  {
    "front": "aware",
    "back": "a. 意识到的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/əˈweːɹ/"
  },
  {
    "front": "benefit",
    "back": "n. 利益",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈbɛn.ɪ.fɪt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "capable",
    "back": "a. 有能力的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈkeɪpəbl̩/"
  },
  {
    "front": "capacity",
    "back": "n. 容量，能力",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəˈpæsɪti/"
  },
  {
    "front": "category",
    "back": "n. 种类",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈkætəˌɡɔɹi/"
  },
  {
    "front": "challenge",
    "back": "n. 挑战",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈtʃæl.əndʒ/"
  },
  {
    "front": "chemical",
    "back": "a. 化学的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈkɛmɪkəl/"
  },
  {
    "front": "circumstance",
    "back": "n. 环境，情况",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/-æns/"
  },
  {
    "front": "cite",
    "back": "vt. 引用",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/saɪt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "civil",
    "back": "a. 公民的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈsɪv.əl/"
  },
  {
    "front": "clarify",
    "back": "vt. 澄清",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈklæɹɪfaɪ/"
  },
  {
    "front": "classic",
    "back": "a. 经典的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈklæ.sɪk/"
  },
  {
    "front": "clause",
    "back": "n. 条款",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/klɔːz/"
  },
  {
    "front": "code",
    "back": "n. 法典，代码",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəʊd/"
  },
  {
    "front": "coherent",
    "back": "a. 连贯的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/koːˈhiɹənt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "coincide",
    "back": "vi. 一致",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˌkoʊɪnˈsaɪd/"
  },
  {
    "front": "collapse",
    "back": "vi. 倒塌",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəˈlæps/"
  },
  {
    "front": "colleague",
    "back": "n. 同事",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈkɒliːɡ/"
  },
  {
    "front": "commence",
    "back": "vt. 开始",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəˈmɛns/"
  },
  {
    "front": "comment",
    "back": "n. 评论",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈkɒmɛnt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "commission",
    "back": "n. 委员会",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəˈmɪʃən/"
  },
  {
    "front": "commit",
    "back": "vt. 承诺，犯罪",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəˈmɪt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "communicate",
    "back": "vt. 交流",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəˈmjuːnɪkeɪt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "community",
    "back": "n. 社区",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/k(ə)ˈmjunəti/"
  },
  {
    "front": "compatible",
    "back": "a. 兼容的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəmˈpætəbəl/"
  },
  {
    "front": "compensate",
    "back": "vt. 补偿",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈkɒm.pən.seɪt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "compile",
    "back": "vt. 汇编",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəmpʌɪl/"
  },
  {
    "front": "complement",
    "back": "vt. 补充",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈkɒmpləmənt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "complex",
    "back": "a. 复杂的",
    "note": "IELTS"
  },
  {
    "front": "component",
    "back": "n. 成分",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kʌmˈpoʊnənt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "compound",
    "back": "n. 化合物",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˈkɒmpaʊnd/"
  },
  {
    "front": "comprehensive",
    "back": "a. 综合的",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/ˌkɒm.pɹɪˈhɛn.sɪv/"
  },
  {
    "front": "comprise",
    "back": "vt. 包含",
    "note": "IELTS",
    "phonetic": "/kəmˈpɹaɪz/"
  }
]